[{"status": "Official", "date": "2000-12-01", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "This Is Not a Film", "asin": "B00005AM98", "country": "US", "artist": "689e13ff-0a6d-4b19-9a79-73532d597967", "quality": "normal", "id": "50919612-79da-4755-ad3e-f8e27c5eb597", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2000-12-01", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1999-10", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "RED.", "country": "US", "artist": "689e13ff-0a6d-4b19-9a79-73532d597967", "quality": "normal", "id": "8c47278d-f4a7-4585-b6dc-c28579ba5599", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1999-10", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1997-09-30", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "The Best Of", "asin": "B000007N02", "country": "US", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "barcode": "0015707050722", "quality": "normal", "id": "15e78feb-ca71-4084-aca6-5ddc6b712943", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1997-09-30", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1969", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Flowers in the Valley", "country": "GB", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "quality": "normal", "id": "418a426d-2994-3662-88ef-6ce15e7f5116", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1969", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1970", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Flowers in the Valley", "country": "US", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "quality": "normal", "id": "48c088d1-3e55-4ed9-895a-5fdb626e4988", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1970", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2004", "title": "Best of Family & Friends", "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}, "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "asin": "B0001GOHAW", "country": "US", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "030206138825", "quality": "normal", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "id": "53b09c6a-7afc-48f5-beb2-ad0ee12b145a", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2004", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}]}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1972", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Save the Land!", "country": "US", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "quality": "normal", "id": "5b795634-6461-4f27-97bd-fb31bd2d0dd5", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1972", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1972", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "1", "artwork": "true", "front": "true", "back": "false"}, "title": "Show Me the Way", "country": "US", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "quality": "normal", "id": "5ee53f36-d465-4d97-a2cc-fd79267d7ed2", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1972", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1970", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Welcome to Our House", "asin": "B0046O1JQK", "country": "US", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "quality": "normal", "id": "608b6268-713f-47eb-8a0f-58f681e477ad", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1970", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1993", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Christmas", "asin": "B0000028Q7", "country": "US", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "barcode": "0074645283227", "quality": "normal", "id": "6b76a617-d8e0-33a2-a022-0983b297133d", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1993", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1969", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Christmas", "country": "US", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "quality": "normal", "id": "c49a26ea-c3be-4e6e-b0b1-20da57d66247", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1969", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1988", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Live!", "asin": "B000000ELV", "country": "US", "artist": "530846f0-4098-4d33-bd8a-8611f823bf51", "quality": "normal", "id": "dc1bea60-4b4f-4233-a8fb-62863beb15b8", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1988", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2008-12-16", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Vibes", "asin": "B001KNUQ32", "country": "US", "artist": "41c0869f-dfe6-46cc-aa35-cbe9f29638cf", "barcode": "860449000005", "quality": "normal", "id": "5ccb7c75-10d6-4196-9da9-e54d365572be", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2008-12-16", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1997-04-22", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Waterbed Hev", "asin": "B000005AYV", "country": "US", "artist": "41c0869f-dfe6-46cc-aa35-cbe9f29638cf", "quality": "normal", "id": "61900d06-de02-4ece-a37f-7865278e1655", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1997-04-22", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1999-06-15", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Heavy", "country": "US", "artist": "41c0869f-dfe6-46cc-aa35-cbe9f29638cf", "quality": "normal", "id": "985eeebf-d9e2-459d-a539-63a72a382595", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1999-06-15", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2008-12-16", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Vibes", "country": "US", "artist": "41c0869f-dfe6-46cc-aa35-cbe9f29638cf", "quality": "normal", "id": "c9caaf3f-ce6e-44c8-904c-083e25c29b28", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2008-12-16", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1999-03-20", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "The Simpsons Sing the Blues", "asin": "B000000OZV", "country": "GB", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "barcode": "720642430828", "quality": "normal", "id": "02b17241-c8c4-309f-8e09-890187332305", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1999-03-20", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1997", "title": "Songs in the Key of Springfield: Original Music From the Television Series", "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}, "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "asin": "B0000033Z8", "country": "US", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "081227272326", "quality": "normal", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "9", "artwork": "true", "front": "true", "back": "false"}, "id": "12d0310c-e2d4-4712-97fb-5a09b6b15381", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1997", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}]}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1999-03-20", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "The Simpsons Sing the Blues", "asin": "B000000OZV", "country": "GB", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "barcode": "720642430828", "quality": "normal", "id": "26b9fd9a-2055-3d51-b1c9-e14c3b24fd9f", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1999-03-20", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1990", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "8", "artwork": "true", "front": "true", "back": "true"}, "title": "The Simpsons Sing the Blues", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "country": "XE", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "720642430828", "quality": "normal", "id": "3b505c55-1872-4871-99bd-e06671d4af12", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1990", "area": {"name": "Europe", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["XE"], "id": "89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a", "sort-name": "Europe"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2007-07-17", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Testify", "asin": "B000TUC4FA", "country": "GB", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "barcode": "5099950557929", "quality": "normal", "id": "3f125293-bad1-32ae-b989-8941506e07a2", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2007-07-17", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2007", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Testify", "country": "XE", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "quality": "normal", "id": "4cf44c4d-06d2-438e-b6cb-0ab2db1c6a55", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2007", "area": {"name": "Europe", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["XE"], "id": "89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a", "sort-name": "Europe"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2007-09-18", "title": "Testify: A Whole Lot More Original Music From the Television Series", "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}, "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "asin": "B000TXZVGG", "country": "US", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "826663105377", "quality": "normal", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "id": "5c580f75-afca-464f-8a72-13a14e95a8f5", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2007-09-18", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}]}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1997-06-30", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Songs in the Key of Springfield", "asin": "B0000033Z8", "country": "GB", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "barcode": "081227272326", "quality": "normal", "id": "5d1f5ac8-98a5-3284-9558-c54ffcd01485", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1997-06-30", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1999-11-02", "title": "Go Simpsonic With the Simpsons: More Original Music From the Television Series", "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}, "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "asin": "B00001WRKM", "country": "US", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "081227548025", "quality": "normal", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "id": "7963b959-6492-3d53-bcad-d0b000dd18ab", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1999-11-02", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}]}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2014-04-01", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "1", "artwork": "true", "front": "true", "back": "false"}, "title": "Testify: A Whole Lot More Original Music From the Television Series", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "country": "US", "packaging": "None", "quality": "normal", "id": "7c515aa7-f2f4-41e6-a3aa-c84e31589a58", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2014-04-01", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1990-02-02", "title": "The Simpsons Sing the Blues", "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}, "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "asin": "B000008KPZ", "country": "US", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "075992430821", "quality": "normal", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "1", "artwork": "true", "front": "true", "back": "false"}, "id": "948e7555-e33a-4c8d-a630-b656c60bef59", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1990-02-02", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}]}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2001", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Songs in the Key of Springfield & Go Simpsonic With the Simpsons", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "081227352929", "quality": "normal", "id": "9cc950bb-b42e-4165-8112-deb0574a9d13", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2001"}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1998-11-24", "title": "The Yellow Album", "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}, "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "asin": "B00000FEOB", "country": "US", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "720642448021", "quality": "normal", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "id": "a55a759b-703d-434a-b5ee-8ba457ccf6db", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1998-11-24", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}]}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1999-11-08", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Go Simpsonic With the Simpsons", "asin": "B00003Q4E2", "country": "GB", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "barcode": "081227528027", "quality": "normal", "id": "cdcd30d8-9edd-4a3b-b82a-db7f662b1657", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1999-11-08", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "release-event-count": 1, "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}, "title": "Songs in the Key of Springfield: Original Music From the Television Series", "artist": "eca1f8ea-52af-4e33-959a-12a59e12adab", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "1", "artwork": "true", "front": "true", "back": "false"}, "country": "US", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "", "quality": "normal", "disambiguation": "BMG club edition", "id": "ec37dd2b-3afd-4362-a70a-9f6fa94b932b", "date": "1997-03-18", "release-event-list": [{"date": "1997-03-18", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}]}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1997-10", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "New York Rhythms", "asin": "B0000080DX", "country": "GB", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "quality": "normal", "id": "064c24b0-98a6-4f75-ad79-c3e6d18a648e", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1997-10", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2004", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Essential Elements", "asin": "B0001XAM7C", "country": "US", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "barcode": "788557024020", "quality": "normal", "id": "1b47aef9-b870-4a80-9976-602e9fe1256e", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2004", "area": {"name": "United States", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "sort-name": "United States"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1998-10", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "New York Rhythms, Volume Two", "asin": "B00004TVY4", "country": "GB", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "quality": "normal", "id": "3d93a08a-e842-4aec-ab7b-9e6ca3459ce7", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1998-10", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2003-03-24", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Enter Our World", "country": "GB", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "quality": "normal", "id": "439ec2aa-349f-4b83-b04b-c452a081b481", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2003-03-24", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1999-09", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "4", "artwork": "true", "front": "true", "back": "true"}, "title": "The Many Shades of Mateo & Matos", "asin": "B00002MDY0", "country": "GB", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "barcode": "689492000028", "quality": "normal", "id": "65db31a5-cc13-49d0-9084-28153d0a8bb1", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1999-09", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2001", "title": "Classic Inspirations", "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}, "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "asin": "B01AB81Q58", "country": "GB", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "barcode": "689492009229", "quality": "normal", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "id": "9700f165-0e68-445c-a73b-5f7fac9927bd", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2001", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}]}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1999-09", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Many Shades of Mateo & Matos", "asin": "B000031KHX", "country": "GB", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "quality": "normal", "id": "a4641992-d43f-40c7-8e74-460a71678a8f", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1999-09", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1998-10", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "New York Rhythms, Volume Two", "asin": "B00004TVY4", "country": "GB", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "quality": "normal", "id": "aed5c5f0-1f40-42c3-ad54-14754838011f", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1998-10", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2005", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Bargrooves: Manhattan", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "quality": "normal", "id": "bad8679c-58c0-4565-bd7f-d6fcb6fbec05", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2005"}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "2001-04", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "Inspirations", "asin": "B00005B9JT", "country": "GB", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "barcode": "689492008727", "quality": "normal", "id": "ce219973-4943-4e67-9bd0-cbc6329fb03a", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "2001-04", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}, {"status": "Official", "date": "1998-10", "cover-art-archive": {"count": "0", "artwork": "false", "front": "false", "back": "false"}, "title": "New York Rhythms, Volume Two", "country": "GB", "artist": "64e22e24-7196-466e-a800-49cf3c4ba59a", "quality": "normal", "id": "fba630d6-fe5c-432d-bdf8-a335d7fe311c", "release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"date": "1998-10", "area": {"name": "United Kingdom", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["GB"], "id": "8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed", "sort-name": "United Kingdom"}}], "text-representation": {"script": "Latn", "language": "eng"}}]